Ashish Choudhary

Sr. Software engineer

ashish.choudhary84@gmail.com

Summary

I am a Front End Engineer and User Experience Designer. I have 7 + years of work experiences in web /Mobile development. Mainly worked with HTML, CSS, Angularjs, PhoneGap, Adobe Flex (3, 4, 4.5 Mobile and Adobe Air Application), ASP .NET, Microsoft Expression Web 3 (Front End development) and GWT (Google web toolkit) frameworks with UiBinder.

I am presently looking for growth opportunities in UI Development and is willing to focus on Reactjs, Angularjs, HTML5 CSS 3, Scss and Less etc. They are considered to be the future of web technologies.

Experience

Senior Software Engineer at William O'Neil India June 2016 - Present

SR Front End Developer at Vinfotech
June 2010 - June 2016 (6 years 1 month)

work status :-

- 1. Worked on Angularjs, Sencha touch and phoneGap Applications.
- 2. Expertise in Adobe Flex Builder 3, 4, AND 4.5 mobile(UI development)
- 3. Good knowledge In GWT (Google web toolkit) frameworks with UiBinder .
- 4. Competence knowledge of Microsoft Expression web (Front end development).
- 5. Good knowledge in HTML & commencement of Responsive Web and HTML5 Frameworks Jquery, Java Script, Handlebar.
- 6. Knowledge of Adobe Dreamweaver CS5 (layout designing)
- 7. Resolute knowledge of Adobe Photoshop CS5 & hand on Adobe Fireworks CS5.
- 8. Hand on database integration with Microsoft SQL Server 2008.
- 9. Working on Cairngorm Framework (Application architecture in Adobe Flex)
- 10. Basic knowledge of MVC Framework.

Front end developer

June 2010 - June 2016 (6 years 1 month)

Ui, Front end developer and Web developer

Education

Devi Ahilya Vishwavidyalaya

Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.), E-Commerce/Electronic Commerce, 2006 - 2008 Government Mahakoshal Arts & Commerce Autonomous College, Jabalpur, Madhya Pradesh Bachelor's Degree, B-com, 2002 - 2005

saraswati shishu mandir jabalpur

High School, Bcom, 2000 - 2002

Ashish Choudhary

Sr. Software engineer

ashish.choudhary84@gmail.com



Contact Ashish on LinkedIn